[mid-tempo rock plays]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
[people chattering. laughing]
Oh. what up. Look at you two!
All right! Yeah! Yeah.
Hey!
Drink!
You lost!
Okay. cheers. Chicks.
Kate. it's your turn.
Should I text her?
Liz Murphy needs to stop
posting pics of her food.
We get it. Liz. you're vegan.
I don't know.
I was thinking of trying it.
Not me. I like to eat
what I want when I want.
Isn't that how you get fat?
Too many calories is how you get
fat. and I never go over 1.200. See?
I need that.
What's that called?
"Countdown to Skinny." It's so good.
It totally works.
Are we not playing
the game anymore?
Is it this one?
No. That's weird.
What is that?
"If you could know exactly when you were
going to die. would you want to know?"
That's creepy.
- That's literally all it says.
- Awesome!
Okay. new game.
Let's all download it.
and whoever is gonna die first has to
finish all the drinks on the table.
- I'm in.
- All right. I'm so down.
I'm out.
I'm not messing with that.
Don't be such
a little beyotch.
It's just an app.
Okay.
- [boy] It's this app?
- Mm-hmm.
One second.
- Everybody ready?
- Let's do it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I got 63 years.
Oh!
Nice. Mine says 32.
I got 22 years. YOLO!
What's yours say. Court?
Court?
Um. it says I only have
three hours to live.
You're gonna die!
Oh!
You lost! Drink up.
- Oh. my God. Evan. get over here.
- What?
We downloaded an app that
tells us when we're gonna die.
Look at your girlfriend's.
- Why would you download that?
- I don't know. We all were.
You better not kill
my best friend.
You guys are ridiculous.
- Drink up. Court.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- You lost.
- What?
- You did lose a bet. so you gotta drink.
- Chug! Come on. Court.
These are all full.
Are you kidding me?
I got you. babe.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Look at that.
Chivalry is not dead.
- Lighten up.
- Yeah. I'll go.
It was Kate's...
[Evan giggles]
Oh! [blows raspberry]
Babe. you can't drive.
You're wasted.
[blows raspberry] You know I
drive way better when I'm drunk.
That's not funny.
I'm kidding.
Let's just walk to my house.
Oh. my God.
Please don't tell me you're still
worried about that stupid app.
Baby. I swear.
I'm not gonna kill you.
I know.
Come on.
Let's leave the car here.
I hate when you do this.
[sighs]
Okay. You know what?
Fine. I'll walk by myself.
Courtney. Courtney. come on.
Courtney. come on! I'm fine!
Get in the car!
Please don't do this.
I told you I'm walking.
Fine. Whatever!
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
Stupid thing.
- [phone: woman screams. sinister laugh]
- [panting]
[panting]
[phone whirring]
[phone: woman screaming.
sinister laugh]
Stop!
[panting continues]
[water runs]
[faint jingling]
[water running]
[phone: woman screaming.
sinister laugh]
- [loud clattering]
- [Courtney screams]
[phone dings]
♪ Give it to the sunshine ♪
♪ I wanna see the water
With my own eyes ♪
♪ You know I like that ♪
♪ Yeah I like that ♪
Thank you.
♪ Get a taste of the good life
Go a little wild On the inside ♪
- Not bad.
- Yeah.
♪ I'll never look back ♪
Quinn.
can you take over this IV?
Oh. sure.
Don't worry.
She's one of our best interns.
♪ Feel something good ♪
♪ Feel. feel something good ♪
Hey. I told you
you can't keep coming in here.
There's asbestos and lead.
and God knows what.
Just one more minute. please?
Okay. Fine. Just one minute.
Just so you know. if something in
here kills me. I am haunting you.
It's normal to be nervous.
Surgery can be scary.
But you're gonna be fine.
I promise.
It's not that.
I mean. it is that. but...
Forget it.
You'll think I'm a psycho.
Ooh. Now you have to tell me.
Can't just dangle the word
"psycho" and not tell me.
I don't get it.
It's an app that tells you
when you're gonna die.
Dude. seriously?
I know. I said the same thing.
But it knew
we were gonna crash.
Wait. there was someone else
in the car with you?
No. she didn't get in. um.
because that app said she was
gonna die in nine minutes.
and nine minutes later I crashed my car
and a tree branch went through her seat.
So. you feel
like she would have died.
But she didn't. right?
What does that tell you about your app?
She did die.
She died that same night.
It knew. all right?
It was right about her.
And now it's saying that I'm gonna
die during that surgery. so...
Listen to me.
You're smart enough to know
that this app was made by some
loser in his parents' basement
trying to scare people.
Come on.
Your minute's up.
[sighs] Evan.
I told you that's off-limits.
You can't keep
going back there.
He knows.
He just needed
a minute to himself.
Mm-hmm.
Follow me.
Shit.
Surprise!
We heard you passed your test.
[man]
You're officially one of us.
- [chanting] One of us. One of us.
- Okay. Okay.
- Freaks.
- You're a freak.
Oh. my God.
- Thank you.
- You earned it.
Is that slice number three?
Yep.
So you want diabetes. then?
My grandfather drank
two cases of Coke a week.
and he lived to 94.
So. I'm good.
You know. there's an app for that.
in case you wanna know for sure.
Did the kid in 237
show you that. too?
Why would anyone wanna know
when they're gonna die?
I wanna know.
What's it called?
Countdown. I think.
I don't think God
intends us to know that.
God has a plan for all of us.
It's not really our place
to question when.
Thank you. It's not natural.
Shit! I'm only gonna make it
to 87. Got robbed. kid.
I'm gonna send it to you guys.
[woman]
I don't want that on my phone.
Fifty-seven years.
That'll make me... 98.
- That's bullshit!
- Is it?
I ran six miles this morning.
How many did you run?
Zero. But I'm still gonna
make it to 87. So. I win.
Ah. [laughs]
Help! I need help.
- Hey. easy. easy.
- Back up. back up.
- What did she take?
- I don't know.
- How long has she been like this?
Let's get
two milligrams of Narcan.
Quinn. grab me the OPRK.
Please. Come on. please.
- What is that?
- It's gonna counteract the drugs.
As long as
she's not too far gone.
- Come on. baby.
- Come on.
Hey. if you're gonna do it.
do it now.
- Okay. Here we go.
- Check. Check.
Come on. Come on.
It's coming. It's coming.
- [man] There you go. There she is.
- [gagging]
Easy. easy. easy.
There you go.
Easy. Welcome back.
We got cake for you.
- [gasping]
- Easy. You're gonna be okay.
There you go. Easy. easy.
[woman on PA announcing]
[elevator bell dings]
You won't be needing this student
badge anymore. Nurse Harris.
Thanks.
So. where do you wanna continue
the celebration tonight?
Oh. I can't.
I just really wanna finish
my paperwork.
But rain check.
I'm proud of you.
[elevator bell dings]
Gonna hold you
to that rain check.
[Quinn] Hey. Scott.
Quick question. I'm just
trying to fill out my I-9.
What do I do
if I don't have a passport?
Just use your birth certificate.
You have that. right?
No. But I think I know where it is.
Hey. Can I call you back?
- Yeah. sure.
- Okay. Bye.
Shit.
[man on TV chattering. faint]
[sighs]
[faint thump]
[gasps]
Jesus. Jordan!
- You scared the crap out of me!
- Shh. You're gonna wake Dad.
What the hell
are you doing in a closet?
[sneezes]
This is Joe.
You wanna put a shirt on. Joe?
Very much so.
Hmm. I think I should go.
I think that's a good idea.
It was really nice meeting...
[door opens]
You shouldn't have boys
coming over.
You can't tell me what to do.
You're not Mom.
Well. if I was. you wouldn't even
think about pulling this shit.
What are you
even doing here. Quinn?
I had to come home
to grab some stuff for work.
And let me guess.
Now that you have it. you're leaving?
See you in another
six months. then. Cool.
Jordan.
[knocking]
- Jordan.
- Go away.
I got some good news today.
I'm officially a nurse.
- Good for you.
- [man] Quinny Bear?
Is everything okay?
It's fine. I'm sorry. Dad.
I didn't mean to wake you.
Hey. come here.
[chuckles]
You hungry? You want me
to heat you something up?
I'm okay. I'm actually headed out.
I have a really early morning.
Hey. If you have any time
on Saturday.
we're gonna go lay some fresh
flowers up on your ma's grave.
Um...
Okay. Sure. Sounds nice.
Great. All right.
We'll pick you up Saturday.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Bye. Dad.
- See you. I love you. sweetie.
- Love you.
[ring tone chiming]
Hello?
[nurse]
Okay. Two-minute warning.
So. if you need to
use the bathroom. use it now.
You'd be surprised how many people
say. "I'm good."
and then it's cleanup
on aisle five.
[laughing]
You need any help?
No. I got it.
All right. I'll be right back.
No freaking way.
[nurse] Hey. I'm at work.
Can I call you back?
Okay. Bye.
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
[crutch clatters]
- [shatters]
- [gasps]
[panting]
[pounding on door]
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
What the hell?
[door squeaks open]
[thudding sound]
[footsteps on stairs]
Courtney?
Court?
[Evan screams]
[woman crying]
Hey. What's going on?
There was an accident.
The patient died in a stairwell.
They think he might have jumped.
Who was it?
The kid from 237.
- Evan?
- Yeah.
You okay?
Yeah.
Um...
Have they packed up
his room yet?
- Hey. Rach.
- Nurse Amy needs to see you.
She just told me
to do this room.
It's okay. I'll take care of it.
You should go see what she wants.
All right. Thanks.
[beeps]
[chiming]
[gasps]
[ticking]
[phone rings]
Hey. Quinny.
Hey. Dad. So. um. you know.
this thing on Saturday.
I checked with the hospital.
and it turns out I do have to work.
That's okay.
You know. work's important.
We can go
another weekend. right?
Yeah. In fact.
this works out great.
Your uncle. Doug.
he's crewing up for a job upstate.
It's good overtime.
- We'll do it when I come back.
- Okay. Thanks. Dad. Love you.
I love you too. Quinny.
- Bye.
No personal calls
when you're on the clock.
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Better not.
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
- [gasps]
- Sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Ms. Thompson's IV drip
stopped.
- Mind taking a look?
- Of course.
This poor lady's
been in a coma for weeks.
[blows]
I know. It's sad.
I think the IV pump
just needs to be reset.
Shit.
- You all right there. kiddo?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
Actually. no.
Hey. hey. hey.
Hey. It's okay.
- It's okay. Talk to me.
- No.
What's the matter?
What happened?
It's nothing.
I'm just having a bad day.
I'm sorry.
First day as an RN.
and I'm already messing up.
Hey. Look at me.
You are an incredible nurse.
Okay?
You're smart. You're driven.
Every time you walk into a patient's
room. you make them smile.
That's a gift. okay?
Come here.
First days are hard.
I should get back to work.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
- Sorry.
- Quinn? Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Remember the recommendation letter you
asked me to write for your license?
- Yeah.
- I gushed about you.
[chuckles]
I really wanna kiss you
right now.
Oh. I don't think
that's appropriate.
Hey. hey. hey. It's okay.
Look. Nobody has to know.
okay? It could be our secret.
Quinn. you like
to help people. right?
Maybe we could help
each other.
- I'm really not comfortable.
- Look. Let's...
No! I said no!
Get off of me!
Stop it!
Jesus Christ. Quinn.
What the hell is wrong with you?
I mean. come on.
I see the way you look at me.
What are you.
some kind of tease?
Look...
I'm sorry.
I thought...
That was really
unprofessional. I apologize.
Okay?
Let's just get back
to work. okay?
Sure.
Hey. Nurse Amy?
Yes. Quinn.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Amy. I need an updated
vitals check on Mrs. Klein.
- I'll be right there in a second.
- This is important.
Nurse Amy. Now. please.
Quinn. can we talk
about this some other time?
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
[typing]
Okay. you guys.
this Countdown app thing.
I'm starting to hear things
and see things.
Like. last night.
I saw my cousin
who died in April.
I saw him.
and he started talking to me.
I know it's real.
and it's toying with me
and it's playing with me.
And it's playing this game of
cat and mouse. and I can feel it.
And it's like it's
feeding off of my fears.
My time is up.
And it feels...
Oh. God. Oh. God. Oh. God.
It's here! It's here!
Help! Help!
[screams]
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
[gasping]
[thunder rumbling]
[gasps]
Quinn! What are you doing?
Did you get evicted
or something?
[thunder rumbling]
Jordan. hang on.
Wait a second.
I can't believe you got that
freaked out by a cockroach.
Where is it? In the kitchen?
Oh. my God.
What the hell did you do
to your phone?
Oh. I. um...
I dropped it.
From where. a plane?
You have a notification from
something called "Countdown."
It says you only have
one day left.
One day until what?
Nothing.
Okay.
Why are you acting so weird?
Why aren't you in school?
Dad went on his work trip.
And since it's your fault I'm
stuck being babysat by Mrs. Talbot.
I thought I could stay here.
Oh. Jordan.
now is not a good time.
"If you could know
exactly when you're gonna die.
would you wanna know?"
Oh. my God.
Is that why you've been acting
like such a freak show?
Because an app told you
you only have one day to live?
No. It's fake. obviously.
Well. I wanna know.
Don't!
What is your problem?
I'm sorry you're stuck with Mrs.
Talbot. but you can't stay here.
Come on.
I never ask for anything.
I told you.
it's just not a good time.
God. Ever since Mom died.
you've really sucked
in the big sister department.
Don't do that. Don't try to make
me feel bad to get what you want.
Just so you know. whatever you thought
Joe and I were doing the other night.
we're definitely
gonna be doing it tonight.
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
Ah!
[man] Next.
My phone just quit working.
I can't imagine why.
You always put it down with such grace?
What do we use it for.
primarily?
Mostly just texting
and Facebook.
You have more computing power
in your pocket
than NASA did when they put
a man on the moon.
but you use it for
"mostly texting and Facebook."
This is why humanity's doomed.
You know what? I don't need
your smug "tech guy" attitude.
Where's your manager?
I'm gonna go get him.
Just hang on. Hold on.
Hello. I'm the manager.
Something I can help you with. miss?
You just lost yourself
a customer. smart-ass.
I did? Do you think I'll be
able to find another one. or...
Next!
I need a new phone.
Okay. What kind of specs
are you looking for?
These actually just came in.
Yeah. Sure. That one.
Okay.
If you could just...
wait till I run the card...
All right.
Never mind. I trust you.
Something in your eyes says you're
a normal. completely sane person.
Need me to transfer
a SIM card over?
No! I want all new everything.
- New phone. new number. new service.
- Okay.
Now. off the books. for $100
cash. I could jailbreak it.
You can have every app
you'll ever need.
No. I just want it
however it comes.
- Okay.
- [door bell jingles]
Here you go.
[sighing heavily]
That's good?
Anything else
I can help you with?
No.
Okay.
- [phone: woman screams. sinister laugh]
- Next.
- What the hell is this?
- What?
This app!
Why is it on there?
That's weird. Did you buy it?
When could I have done that?
You literally just turned it on.
Okay. Deep breath.
Um...
We'll just delete it. Here.
It won't let you delete it!
Just give it to me.
All right. We're on Yelp.
Doc's Wireless.
Please leave a review.
Appreciate it.
Hey. What app
was she talking about?
[engine starts]
Hey! Watch where you're going!
- Sorry.
- Stupid bitch.
I'm sorry.
[car door closes]
- [screams]
- [tires screech]
[gasping]
You again? Are you an idiot?
Look what you did to my Lexus!
Hey! I'm talking to you!
[whistles] Hey! Hey!
Let her go.
- What are you gonna do about it?
- What am I gonna do about it?
You can leave
and nobody gets hurt.
Or you can stick around and find
out that I'm all sorts of crazy.
And I mean the type of crazy where
I just found out I'm gonna die.
and maybe I feel like
taking a white man with me.
So. the choice is yours.
I really don't give a damn.
Relax. man. It was just
a fender bender. Jesus.
- [engine starts]
- You okay?
You're seeing stuff too.
aren't you?
So am I.
What I wanna know is. why us?
Because we downloaded it.
No. that's not it.
Other people download it.
and they find they're living to be 100.
It told me
I violated the user agreement.
Right. You know.
it said the same thing to me.
Did you read it?
The terms and conditions?
Every word.
Really?
No.
You wanna buy a ticket
to Antarctica? Hmm?
Well. you can't.
Because only the government and the
Illuminati have access to Antarctica.
See? The sons of bitches!
Okay.
What if we go somewhere else?
No. it's okay. There's nowhere
to go back and read it.
I think that there's gotta be
something there that could tell us.
You people need to wake up.
Because if we go there.
we'll be able to see that Antarctica
is the edge of the flat earth.
[bartender] I guess
anything's possible. Ger.
What if there's a way for us to
look at that user agreement again?
Hey. track with me.
What if we got someone
to download it
just so we could see the
terms. and we don't accept it?
No! That is wrong.
Trust me.
Hey. question for you guys.
Have any of you heard about this new app
that tells you when you're gonna die?
Sounds like bullshit.
Or maybe that's just
what they want you to think.
Anyway. it's called Countdown.
I don't feel good about this.
It's fake.
Like the Holocaust. huh?
Never mind. Go ahead.
Thank you.
"Camera. Microphone.
Location."
Yeah. yeah. yeah. It's fine.
"User agreement.
Accept terms and conditions?"
Wait. wait. wait!
Are you crazy?
You should never accept the terms and
conditions without reading them first.
Okay. "User shall use
the application."
Yada. yada. yada.
"User shall accept
the terms of his or her fate.
Any attempt to use information derived
from Countdown to alter the user's fate
will result in
a breach of this agreement."
Accept the terms of our fate.
Hang on.
I was supposed to take a train
tomorrow to go see my aunt.
but the app said that's when I
was going to die. so I canceled.
I canceled something. too.
a trip with my sister and my dad.
Maybe this is when I was
supposed to actually die.
Gerry. don't agree to that.
Trust me.
You don't wanna know.
So. no matter what we do.
we're gonna be dead in a couple of hours.
[Gerry laughs]
Well. well. well.
Looks like old Ger Bear's
gonna live to be 91.
Figures.
Let's go.
I love this app.
[elevator bell dings]
Whatever's happening to us.
we think
it's because of this app.
From what I've read online
about hauntings.
there are spirits
and then there are...
demons.
But I don't know. That's why
I wanted to talk to an expert.
Yeah. I mean. it seems
like demon stuff to me.
Well. when we talk about demons.
we're usually speaking metaphorically.
Wait a minute.
So you don't think demons
are real?
I'm sorry. but no.
Look. this stuff...
It's not really what I do.
But I know someone who
might be a little better...
qualified.
Hey. Quinn. Can I talk to you
for a second?
Right. I wanted to talk to you
about yesterday.
Give me two minutes.
Yeah. Great.
Because I have
all the time in the world.
And now I'm talking to myself.
Uh. Yeah. hey. this one's taken.
Yo. buddy. I said this one's
taken. Use another...
Hey. kid. use another stall.
[sighs]
[boy crying]
You okay in there?
Hey. buddy. do you want me
to get you some help?
[crying continues]
[panting]
[boy laughing]
[laughing continues]
Matt.
- [grunts]
- Where is it. Matt? Where is it?
[panting]
- Hey. you all right... Jesus. You're good.
- [gasps]
Okay.
Wow.
I haven't worked here that long.
and that Dr. Sullivan
is this integral...
Quinn. have a seat.
Okay.
This is Dave Andrews from HR.
Emily.
our hospital administrator.
and you know Dr. Sullivan.
Dr. Sullivan
told us what happened.
He did?
Yes. Quinn.
I felt obligated to come clean
and tell them the truth.
This doesn't have to destroy
anyone's life. right?
It was a simple
misunderstanding. that's all.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
But you cornering me
in my office like that.
that wasn't okay.
It needs to be addressed.
I cornered you?
Look. you don't
need to be embarrassed.
I'm just trying to stop something
before it escalates. that's all.
Today's world of "he said.
she said." you can't be too cautious.
I have to protect myself
and my practice.
And the hospital.
Well. based on
Dr. Sullivan's report.
I've recommended
an immediate suspension.
- What?
- Is that necessary?
Can't we just do counseling.
or transfer her...
I don't believe this.
He is the one who cornered me.
What?
I don't get a say in this?
Quinn. if this is true.
why didn't you just come to me right away?
I tried. but that asshole
beat me to it!
We're trying to help you.
Quinn.
Don't make it worse by lying.
Don't touch me!
She seems like
a very unstable young woman.
We're leaving.
Matt. come on.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
[boy laughing]
[bell dings]
[laughing continues]
[Quinn] Hello?
Hello?
Can we get
some service out here?
Yo. will you show
a little bit of respect?
Jesus. Shit!
Shh! Do you hear that?
[speakers] ♪ Panini
Don't you be a meanie ♪
♪ Thought you wanted me
To go ♪
♪ Why you tryna
Keep me teeny? ♪
♪ It's a dreamy... ♪
Hello. Hi.
Hallelujah! I'm starving.
You guys got my Grubhub?
No.
No. We just have to ask you
a question.
Do you believe in demons?
Big time.
Look. I know
how hard this is to believe.
No. no. no.
I mean. yes.
It's hard to believe.
but I want it to be true.
I mean. I don't want you guys to...
[imitates choking] of course.
But demons. whoo!
I mean. that's kind of what got me
into the cloth in the first place.
Do you know. demons are mentioned
in 19 of the 27 books of the Bible?
Yeah. The Gadarene Swine.
the Simon Magus. the apocrypha.
I'm sorry. I don't mean to be
geeking out on you. Just ahh!
I love this stuff.
I mean. the Bible is like
the ultimate graphic novel.
You know. this whole thing reminds
me of this old story from...
♪ Amen ♪
♪ Ah ♪
Yes!
So. there was
this young prince
whose father. a much-beloved king.
was old. like brink-of-death old.
With the King
in such bad shape.
it was up to the prince
to lead the army into battle.
So he tracks down
this old gypsy woman.
And he asks her if she can tell
him. will he survive the battle?
The gypsy woman hands him a
scroll with a number on it.
And that number is
the exact moment of his death.
But she warns him.
"Don't use this
to save yourself.
to change your fate."
Now. the prince agrees.
opens up the scroll.
News ain't good.
not even a little bit.
So you know what he does?
Come here.
He sends
his little brother instead.
But his brother doesn't die.
In fact. he goes on
to lead the army to victory.
Meanwhile. our coward prince
goes back to the old gypsy woman.
and he swears to her.
"The angel of death is coming for me."
But she assures him
Death is not coming for him.
What's coming for him now.
there's nothing natural about it.
It's the demon. Ozhin.
The moment the prince changed his
fate. Ozhin came for him.
But not to kill him.
to torment him
right up until the exact moment
the gypsy predicted he would die.
Oh. Thanks. Father.
I didn't think
I could feel any worse.
Look. I think...
I mean. I'm not sure.
but this app seems like a modern
version of what the old gypsy lady did.
If I could just see the code.
I think I would know for sure.
You mean like hack the app?
Do you know how to do that.
or do you guys know someone who could?
I think I might.
Where the heck's my Grubhub?
[bell jingles]
- [Quinn] Hey. wait! Wait!
- We are closed.
We met earlier. and you said that
you could jailbreak my phone.
Does that mean you know
how to hack into an app?
- Yeah.
- Great.
Look. we need your help.
It's kind of an emergency.
Sorry.
I'm already running late
to my Tinder date.
and I haven't matched with
anybody in a while. So. no.
Wait. wait. wait. You really
wanna impress this girl?
This credit card
has a $2.000 limit.
Yeah. And this one
has about 300 left.
If you help us.
these are yours.
Please.
This feels illegal.
- I like it.
- [bell jingles]
Sorry. It's just gonna be.
I don't know. 15 minutes. okay?
I love your profile pic and I cannot
wait to see the real thing in person.
[chuckles] Okay. Bye-bye.
All right.
You got 15 minutes. Phone?
It's this app. right here.
Seriously? The Countdown app.
where it tells you when you're gonna die?
- That's so dumb.
- Did you download it?
Of course. Your hysteria
piqued my interest.
It's a great idea.
It's just horrible execution.
I mean. just a random number
with a countdown?
It's not very scary. Though.
it seems like it worked on you two clowns.
Please. please. Just continue.
Okay. Thanks.
[typing]
That's weird. Sixty gigs?
- What does that mean?
- That means it's big.
Like "a season of Game of
Thrones on your phone" big.
Which doesn't make any sense
because it's just a clock.
- Can you still delete it?
- Of course.
This is Doc's.
I'm the doc of technology.
I can do anything.
Ha! Check it out.
Now we're in.
What is that?
"Hoc maledictum te..."
- That's Latin.
- Are you sure?
I went to Catholic high school
for four years. I'm sure.
- What's it say?
- No idea.
Physically. I was there.
but mentally...
Oh. my God.
Last name. first name.
And look. these are their countdowns.
There are so many.
Hey. that's me.
Thirty-two years. 11 days.
Hold on. How long do you guys think
the Marvel Universe will last?
Forty years. 50?
Let's just say 60. to be sure.
There it is.
Holy shit. It's working.
Look at his phone.
It worked.
Okay.
What's your name. pumpkin?
Quinn Harris.
Stop.
That's my sister.
Shit.
Of course she downloaded it.
- Her clock is the same as mine.
- Actually. no.
Hers is three minutes shorter.
See?
Wait a minute. Was she supposed
to be with you tomorrow?
Yes. Shit!
Change hers first.
Got another credit card?
Okay. No. no. no. I'll do it.
I'm a good guy. I'll do it.
[phone buzzes]
You know the rules.
No phones at the table.
- But I was...
- You can have it back in the morning.
I was just looking.
Thank you.
You're a genius!
Yeah. no shit.
Are you still good?
Yep.
I got 71 years left.
You know. I kind of feel bad
that I'm gonna outlive you.
Don't. 95 is way too old.
I'm happy with my 86.
So. should I...
drop you at your car?
Yeah. yeah. sure.
Except for the fact that
my car is right over there.
[chuckling]
I suppose I'll call you.
[chuckles]
Nice. real nice.
Do you wanna be alone tonight?
Not at all.
- Do you mind if I keep these lights on?
- Not at all.
I've been thinking a lot
about what Father John said
about what compelled us to
wanna know when we're gonna die.
Me too.
And?
When I was 10.
my little brother.
Jeff. got really sick.
And we practically lived
at the hospital.
My mom and dad could only focus
on Jeff for those two years.
and I get it.
But at the same time.
I was jealous of all the
attention that he was getting.
He had this toy
that I really wanted.
[chuckles]
This stupid robot dinosaur.
So when he was asleep.
I took it.
I stole
my dying brother's toy.
Jeff. he looked up to me.
And I'm the one
that gets to live to be 95.
Yeah. but you were just a kid.
What about you?
My mom.
She was the glue in our family.
But she was tough.
And...
on one of the many nights
I was grounded.
my best friend
was having this huge party.
And I was so sick
of my mom's shit.
so I went.
My mom.
she went out looking for me.
and one drunk driver later.
she was dead.
Quinn. that's not your fault.
[sighs]
Yeah. Thanks.
You know. you don't have to
sleep on the floor.
All right.
But just so we're clear.
I don't usually jump into bed with
girls that I just met off of an app.
Well. technically.
we met because of an app.
Good point.
[wood creaks]
Matt.
Matt. wake up.
Matt!
Yo. are you calling my name?
- [screaming]
- Oh!
- [screaming continues]
- Quinn. Quinn. Quinn. Relax. Relax.
Quinn. Hey. Hey. Hey.
It was just a nightmare.
[phone:
woman screams. sinister laugh]
No. no. no.
It went back to what it was!
Oh. shit.
So did mine.
Oh. no.
Jordan.
[ringtone chiming]
[ringtone continues chiming]
[snores]
[gasps. pants]
[phone: woman screams.
sinister laugh]
Mrs. Talbot?
[panting]
[female voice] Jordan.
Mom?
Where is she?
Where's your sister?
[wood creaking]
[screams. whimpers]
- Where is she?
- [screams]
[screams]
It's okay! It's me!
There's something in the house.
I know. Let's get out of here.
[Quinn] Hello?
[Matt] Open up!
[Quinn] Father John!
You guys okay?
Did you get the code?
New girl.
I'm gonna shirt on.
Come on.
[reading Latin]
"This curse will come upon you.
will pursue you. and overwhelm you
until you are
utterly destroyed."
This is good.
This is really good.
How is that good?
Because now we know
what we're dealing with.
This is a curse.
Curses come from
the devil and his servants.
Good news: curses can be broken.
Can I get
a hallelujah high five?
Fine.
Look. gang.
Satan is the father of lies.
If you can prove him a liar.
you can break the curse.
What does that mean.
"prove him a liar"?
If you can foil the clock.
prove it wrong.
it should lift the curse
from anyone suffering from it.
So someone has to die
before they're supposed to?
That would get the job done.
But I don't think anybody here
wants to die. right?
So. I'm thinking the opposite.
We need to keep one of you alive
longer than you're supposed to be.
How are we
supposed to do that?
This thing shows up
and we're just supposed to be
like. "Hang on. I need a sec"?
That's exactly what
we're gonna do.
See. there's protection rituals.
prayers that should buy you some time.
All we need to do is beat
the clock by one second.
Have you ever done
anything like this before?
No.
But I've read about it. a lot!
Here!
Got it. Got it. Got it.
Look.
We need to make this
out of salt. right?
Now. once I bless it.
you should be safe inside.
See. no impure spirits are
allowed to cross this circle.
It should...
buy you the time you need.
Great. Well. I just have
one question.
Where are we gonna get
that much salt?
I get mine at Costco.
Follow me! Come on!
Clock's ticking. everybody!
Right here. Let me
just turn the lights on.
Good. Right. Come on.
Now. this is rock salt.
I use it to kill weeds.
Will that work?
Salt is salt. Once I bless it.
we're good... I think.
- What?
- No. we're fine. We're gonna be fine.
What if it just blows
the salt away?
That could absolutely happen.
I didn't think of that.
Goddammit! Sorry.
And I will pray it doesn't.
I have an idea.
Wait. Here.
- Hold this.
- Little small. don't you think?
It's not the size of the cross.
it's the power of the Spirit.
What if we mix it with this?
That is a genius idea. Yes.
Let's clear out a space
right here.
Great. Come on.
Clock's ticking. guys!
I'm gonna make a big circle.
Ten. 15 feet. Come on.
You good? Great. Okay.
All right. gang. Here we go.
Thicker. thicker.
Lord.
bless this salt.
Let Your light hold back the demons
that try to enter our world. Lord.
That's it.
Make that symbol perfect.
Make that as thick as you can.
As thick as you can.
That line right there.
Pretty great! I mean.
it's more of an oval than a circle.
but we're under
a lot of pressure.
Okay. how much time
till Matt dies?
Okay. that symbol's good.
That symbol's good. Okay. that's right.
Correct. I got this.
[breathing heavily]
Hey.
- What if this doesn't work?
- It's going to.
No. but what if it doesn't?
Listen to me.
It's just salt and paint...
That's good.
- I think we should get in the circle.
- Come on!
- Quinn. I'm scared.
- Me too.
Okay. This might actually
be happening right now.
- I'm gonna go with the bigger cross.
- What?
[screeches]
- It's in here!
- Stay close to me.
Strengthen us in
Your power and might. O Lord.
Dress us in Your armor. Lord.
so that we may stand firm against
the machinations of the devil.
Wait. wait.
It's moving above us.
[screeching continues]
- Do you see anything?
- No. You?
No.
Okay. Shh. shh. shh.
Wait. wait! Stay behind me!
[screeches]
It's working! He can't get in!
[speaking Latin]
Go back to hell.
- Where did he go?
Where did he go?
[phone: woman screams.
sinister laugh]
[electronic blaring]
- Turn it off!
- [Matt] I'm trying! I'm trying!
- Matt. turn it off!
- I'm trying!
There!
[Father John] Shut it off!
- [blaring continues]
- Shut it off!
[boy] Where is it. Matt?
[gasps]
Jeffy?
Why'd you take my dinosaur?
Jeffy. I was gonna
give it back. I swear.
No. you weren't.
You're right.
Jeffy. I'm sorry.
Matt! What do you see?
Jeffy. don't go.
Huh?
[grunts. screams]
Matt!
Quinn!
[Quinn screams]
No. Jordan.
don't break the circle!
[grunting]
Matt!
We did it.
He let me go...
Help! Help!
[Father John mutters]
I'll see you soon.
Quinn?
He's gone.
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
No. it makes sense.
It was his time.
Pretty soon
it'll be our time. too.
Please don't say that.
I don't want to. but you
just saw what happened.
- Oh. my God.
- [groaning]
Are you bleeding?
[gasps] You're bleeding!
We need some help in here!
- We need a wheelchair!
- Quinn. what happened?
There was an accident. She has
a puncture to the abdomen.
We got her. We'll get her right in.
Go check in with Rosie.
Okay.
No. Please. Quinn.
don't leave me.
I'm not going anywhere.
I will be right there.
- Please don't leave me. Please.
- I'll be right there.
Sorry. honey. are you okay?
[phone ringing]
Matt's train.
That's not too bad. You're
pretty tough though. right?
Quinn. Hey.
Can I talk to you?
- I really...
- I heard what happened with Dr. Sullivan.
I know what happened.
I mean...
I personally know...
I just want you to know
that if you go after him.
I'm with you.
I think you're gonna be
A-okay. Look at me.
Thank you.
Truly. thank you. Rachel.
All right.
Just like your big sister.
I'll let you two at it.
You'll be in good hands.
kiddo.
Thank you.
Of course.
[gasps]
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Quinn. I know you think
it was your fault.
Mom dying.
It was my fault.
What?
Mom asked me where you were.
and I knew.
And if I had just told her.
she wouldn't have been driving
way over by the mall.
Jordan.
it is not your fault some
drunk asshole ran a red light.
Then it's not your fault.
either.
I think Mom would be happy we're
spending our last few minutes together.
These are not
our last few minutes.
Wait. Quinn.
Trust me.
Quinn!
What are you gonna do? Quinn!
[Dr. Sullivan] No.
I just finished a procedure.
Saving lives
one day at a time.
[laughing]
Okay. honey.
I'll let you get back to work.
I love you. too. Bye.
You shouldn't be in here.
I wanted to thank you
for helping my sister.
And...
say that I'm sorry.
For what?
For everything.
I can't stop thinking about how
things could've gone that day.
I understand
why you did what you did.
I put you in that position.
If only I had followed through with
how I really felt in that moment.
I was just scared.
Bullshit.
[chuckles]
You think I'm stupid? Hmm?
What do you really want?
I want my job back.
You said that
we both like helping people.
So maybe you can help me
and I...
...could help you.
Okay. what are you doing?
You recording this?
Search me if you want.
I'll be in the closed wing.
You should come.
Or don't. It's up to you.
[door closes]
Quinn?
[Quinn] Come find me.
You know. I'm not gonna lie.
I didn't see this one coming.
[sniffs]
[sighs]
You dropped something.
Close your eyes
and say. "Marco."
[laughs] I like this.
Marco.
[Quinn] Polo.
Polo.
[chuckles]
I can hear you breathing.
[grunts] Bitch!
- What the hell is that?
- Morphine.
enough to kill you three times.
you piece of shit!
Quinn. don't!
It's either him or you.
[shouts]
Did you see that? It saved him.
This is gonna work.
What's gonna work?
He has the app.
If he dies before he's supposed
to. it'll break the curse!
Quinn!
[clanging]
Quinn. where are you?
[phone: woman screams.
sinister laugh]
[screams]
[rustling]
[grunts]
[Quinn grunts. breathes heavily]
Crazy bitch!
What the hell was that thing?
Doesn't matter. I'll tell the
cops how you lured me back here.
How I had to kill you
out of self-defense.
[Dr. Sullivan grunts]
Your time's up. you rapey fuck!
- [shouts]
- Shit.
Jordan. Jordan!
[grunts]
Jordan.
[gasping]
[phone: woman screams.
sinister laugh]
I don't wanna die.
[door opens. closes]
- [Jordan screaming]
- [roaring]
[roars]
- [roars]
- [gasps. screams]
[Quinn] Hey!
Get away from her.
[roars]
What are you doing?
I love you. Jordan.
I'll always be with you.
Quinn. don't!
[woman] Quinny Bear.
Mom?
Where were you that night?
I'm so sorry.
I was looking for you.
I know.
I miss you.
I miss you too. baby.
Come here.
[crying]
No.
You're not in control anymore.
I am.
Quinn. no!
Quinn!
[Jordan crying]
No!
[growls. roars]
[roaring. shrieking]
[Jordan gasping]
Somebody help me!
Quinn!
Please.
Please don't leave me.
Please. [crying]
Please.
Come on. come on. come on.
Please work.
Please work. please.
- Quinn. come on.
- [gasps]
See?
I told you
I'd always be with you.
I love you.
[Quinn] Happy birthday. Mom.
They're beautiful.
Oh. my gosh.
Three more women came
forward about Dr. Sullivan.
Looks like he's going away
for a long time.
Good. Serves him right.
I'm just glad
no one else is gonna get hurt.
Coming to the house. Quinny?
I have to stop
at the hospital first.
- You wanna come with me?
- Yeah.
- All right. I'll see you guys at home.
- Cool.
[ringtone chiming]
You coming?
What's wrong?
[mid-tempo rock song plays]
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- [man] A little more?
- No. thank you. No.
Oh. We killed it. [laughs]
I gotta tell you something.
Now that we know each other a little bit.
you are a lot chestier
than your profile pic.
Oh. Thanks.
And you don't look
anything like yours.
- Appreciate that. Thank you.
- At all.
Okay. I revised your check
for the third time.
Also. we closed
a half hour ago. So...
[tutting]
[sighs]
We love it here.
I'm sure you do.
- What a catch.
- Yeah.
I don't know
what your data plan is.
but I can get you a 15.
maybe 20% discount.
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna
use the ladies' room.
Okay. I will be here.
my darling.
Yeah.
[phone: woman screams.
sinister laugh]
[ticks rapidly]
What the hell?
Hello?
Dude. we're still here.
Come on. man.
- Dude.
- [growling]
What the hell?
- [shrieks]
- [screams]